{
	"questions":
	[
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Knight",
			"answer": "Marchog"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Knights",
			"answer": "Marchogion"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Knight",
			"answer": "Y Marchog"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Knights",
			"answer": "Y Marchogion"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Author (M)",
			"answer": "Awdor"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Authors (M)",
			"answer": "Awdoron"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Author (M)",
			"answer": "Yr Awdor"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Authors (M)",
			"answer": "Yr Awdoron"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Author (F)",
			"answer": "Awdures"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Authors (F)",
			"answer": "Awduresau"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Author (F)",
			"answer": "Yr Awdures"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Authors (F)",
			"answer": "Yr Awduresau"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Teacher (M)",
			"answer": "Athro"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Teachers (M)",
			"answer": "Athrawon"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Teacher (M)",
			"answer": "Yr Athro"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Teachers (M)",
			"answer": "Yr Athrawon"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Teacher (F)",
			"answer": "Athrawes"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Teachers (F)",
			"answer": "Athrawesau"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Teacher (F)",
			"answer": "Yr Athrawes"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Teachers (F)",
			"answer": "Yr Athrawesau"
		}
	]
  }
  